{
    "subject": "resource/Vanessa_Bell_Armstrong",
    "predicate": "ontology/hometown",
    "object": "resource/United_States",
    "human_readable": "Vanessa Bell Armstrong's hometown is United States.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9757086038589478,
            "question": "What is significant about the United States being Vanessa Bell Armstrong's hometown?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8938737511634827,
            "question": "Is Vanessa Bell Armstrong originally from the United States?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8847139477729797,
            "question": "What country is Vanessa Bell Armstrong's hometown in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7960216403007507,
            "question": "Is there any connection between Vanessa Bell Armstrong and her hometown?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7151792049407959,
            "question": "What influences might Vanessa Bell Armstrong's hometown have had on her?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6782578825950623,
            "question": "Where was Vanessa Bell Armstrong from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6076769828796387,
            "question": "Did Vanessa Bell Armstrong spend most of her childhood in the United States?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5078012943267822,
            "question": "Where did Vanessa Bell Armstrong grow up?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.31314048171043396,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Vanessa Bell Armstrong's origins?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.24844413995742798,
            "question": "What is known about Vanessa Bell Armstrong's early life?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Vanessa Bell Armstrong's hometown is United States.",
            "html": "dbpedia_9251_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about Vanessa Bell Armstrong's origins?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9251_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where did Vanessa Bell Armstrong grow up?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9251_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Did Vanessa Bell Armstrong spend most of her childhood in the United States?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9251_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9251_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9251_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9251_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9251_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9251_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9251_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9251_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9251_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9251_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9251_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\n**Explanation:** The documents provide information about Vanessa Bell Armstrong\u2019s background, including that she was born in Detroit, Michigan. Detroit is a city located in the United States, so it can be inferred that her hometown is the United States."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}